Guide to the Tri-State Conference on Manufacturing Records, 1978-1993 AIS.1993.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Research, June 1984 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Plant Closings and Relocation, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Pittsburgh, Renaissance II, and Allegheny County Local Economies (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Recession and Unemployment, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- US Steel, Clippings, 1983-1986 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel Co., Clippings, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Armco Steel Co., Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Bethlehem Steel Co., Clippings, 1981-1984 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Eastmet Steel Company, Clippings, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Florida Steel Corp., Clippings, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Foreign Steel Industries, Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Inland Steel Company, Chicago, Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Japanese Steel Companies, Clippings, 1977, 1982-1984 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Kaiser Steel Corp., Clippings, 1982-1984 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- McLouth Steel, Clippings, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Domestic Steel Companies, Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- National Steel Co., Clippings, 1982-1985 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Phoenix Steel Company, Clippings, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Republic/LTV Steel Company, Clippings, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Weirton Steel Co., Clippings, 1982-1984 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Wisconsin Steel Company, Clippings, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Youngstown Plant Shutdowns (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Profiles of Major Suppliers to the Automotive Industry, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Chapter 8: Profit Cycles, Oligopoly and the Geography of Steel (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Steelclips, February 1985 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Data Center Corporate Profile: US Steel (Box 14, Folder 21-22)
- US Steel, Clippings, 1980-1983 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Pittsburgh Area Strikes (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Reagan Administration Personnel (Box 14, Folder 25)
- President Reagan's Policies and Budget Cuts, 1981-1983 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Steel Valley Information, Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Port Authority of Allegheny County (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Taxes, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Newspaper Articles (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Women's Struggles in Steel Industry (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Urban Redevelopment Authority of Pittsburgh (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Steel Industry General Information, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Union Busting, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Mon Valley General Information, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- US Steel Mon Valley Works Information, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- North American Congress on Latin America: Research Methodology Guide (Box 14, Item 1)
- The Price of the Pentagon: The Industrial and Commercial impact of th 1981 Military Budget by Employment Research Associates (Box 14, Item 2)
- Unemployment: Fallout of the Arms Race (Box 14, Item 3)
- El Salvador, Clippings, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Labor Committee for Safe Energy and Full Employment (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Political Mailing List (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Economic Dislocation: Plant Closings, Plant relocations and Plant Conversion, 1979 (Box 14, Item 4)
- Steel Industry Policy (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Anti-War and Anti-Nuclear Activities, 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Foreign Aid, Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Imported Steel, Clippings, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Presidential Candidate Information, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Steel Valley Authority Conference Notes and Transcripts, October 29, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, Resumes for Reagan, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Infrastructure Material, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Financial Records, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Education Committee (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Library Cards (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Justice and Peace (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Just Harvest, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Bishop Bevilacqua's Task Force on Unemployment, 1984-1986 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Economic Development and Industrial Corporation/Boston, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Monongahela Alliance for Community Protection, Morgantown, WV (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Pittsburgh Plate Glass, Inc., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Mahoning Valley JOIN Conference, February 25, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Support Our Neighborhoods Action Coalition, 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Trade Union Action and Democracy/Communist Party USA "Economic Notes" Publications, Information and Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Tactical Research and Investigations Network, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Swissvale Survival Center (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Central America Response Network (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Midland Alive Coalition, Midland-Crucible Plant Shutdown, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Dayton Solidarity, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Arts/Guide to Programs and Services (Box 15, Folder 26)
- ACORN, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- National Coalition Building Institute (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Michlovic, Tom - State Representative for Turtle Creek, Braddock and Duquesne, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Coalition for Safe Subways (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Owens-Corning Fiberglass (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Business of America Brochure (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Dorothy Six Brochures, New Hope for Steel and Steel Valley Authority Residents Education (Box 15, Folder 33)
- How OSHA Monitors State Plants, January 1975 (Box 15, Item 1)
- Vinyl Chloride, Job Health Hazard Series, June 1975 (Box 15, Item 2)
- Essentials of Machine Guarding, Safe Work Practices Series, July 1975 (Box 15, Item 3)
- Mercury, Job Health Hazard Series, August 1975 (Box 15, Item 4)
- Handling Hazardous Materials, Safe Work Practices Series, September 1975 (Box 15, Item 5)
- Commenting on OSHA Standards, March 1976 (Box 15, Item 6)
- Hot Environments, Job Health Hazard Series, 1976 (Box 15, Item 7)
- OSHA: Your Workplace Rights in Action, 1979 (Box 15, Item 8)
- Health Hazards of Inorganic Arsenic, 1979 (Box 15, Item 9)
- Air Pollution: The Facts (Box 15, Item 10)
- Part of the Human Condition: Health and Safety Hazards in the Workplace (Box 15, Item 11)
- The Union is You! The Grievance Committee Handbook by USWA (Box 15, Item 12)
- USWA Safety and Health Program (Box 15, Item 13)
- A Guide to Procedures of the Occupational Safety and Health Review Commission, 1978 (Box 15, Item 14)
- Safety and Health Legislation by USWA, 1978 (Box 15, Item 15)
- Helping Through the Hard Times: A How-To Manual for Union-Sponsored Food Distribution Programs by the Hunger Action Coalition, August 1982 (Box 15, Item 16-19)
- USWA Questions and Answers about the Schweiker-Williams Bill (Box 15, Item 20)
- Safety & Health Update by the USWA Safety and Health Department, 1980 (Box 15, Item 21)
- Ray Marshall, Secretary of Labor v. Whirlpool Corporation and Empire-Detroit Steel Division, Detroit Steel Corporation, February 22, 1979 (Box 15, Item 22)
- Winning at the Occupational Safety and Health Review Commission: Workers' Handbook on Enforcing Safety and Health Standards by Bert Cottine, Linda Birrel and Robert Jennings, 1975 (Box 15, Item 23)
- Federal Register: Occupational Exposure to Lead, 1978 (Box 15, Item 24)
- Body Response to Toxic Substances (Box 15, Item 25)
- USWA Safety or Health Recommendations Forms (Box 15, Item 26)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration Complaint Forms (Box 15, Item 27)
- David Arthur Page, Regional Research (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Dorothy Six Financial Study, Lazard Freres, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- US Steel Response to the Locker/Abrecht Duquesne Works Feasibility Report, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Hollow Corporations Article in Business Week, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Industrial Parks, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Industrial Capital Fund, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Infrastructure Information, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Steel Valley Authority By-Laws (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Democratic Debate Rally, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Ohio Valley Unemployed Committee, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- LTV/Jones & Laughlin, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- LTV/Jones & Laughlin Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 12)
- LTV/Jones & Laughlin Early Information, 1970s-1985 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Mesta (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Grand Concourse Workers, USWA Local 8932, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Armour Workers, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Hormel Workers (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Bakery, Confectionery and Tobacco Union Local 12 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Kroger Workers, United Food and Commercial Workers Local 23, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Steelworkers Benefits, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Steelworkers Labor and Bargaining, Clippings, 1983-1985 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- UMWA/Coal Miners Information and Struggles (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Union Busting: Articles, Information and Organizations, 1980, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Union Information, Clippings, 1983-1985 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers Union (Box 17, Folder 11)
- United Autoworkers (Box 17, Folder 12)
- United Electrical Workers, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- United Mine Workers (Box 17, Folder 14)
- United Food and Commercial Workers (Box 17, Folder 15)
- USWA Activities, 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Concessions, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- USWA Concessions (Box 17, Folder 18-19)
- USWA Imports (Box 17, Folder 20)
- USWA International Convention, Atlantic City, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- USWA Personnel, History and Information (Box 17, Folder 22)
- USWA Rank and File Local Union Activities, US Steel Mon Valley Works Mills, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- USWA, Steelabor Magazine, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- USWA Activities, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- USWA Local 1397 Activities, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 26-27)
- USWA Activities, 1981-1987 (Box 17, Folder 28-31)
- Steel Industry Crisis, Articles and Clippings (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
- US Steel, Disinvestment, Decline/Getting Out of Steel (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Mon Valley, St. Peter's Church (Box 18, Folder 4)
- US Steel, Economic (Box 18, Folder 5)
- USWA Local 1397, Environmental Protection Agency Lawsuits (Box 18, Folder 6)
- US Steel Financial Reports (Box 18, Folder 7)
- US Steel, General Information (Box 18, Folder 8)
- US Steel, History (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Imports (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Mergers and Acquisitions (Box 18, Folder 11)
- US Steel, Personnel (Box 18, Folder 12)
- US Steel, Stockholders' Reports and Activities (Box 18, Folder 13)
- US Steel, Prices and Profit Reports (Box 18, Folder 14)
- US Steel, Government Relations (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Rank and File Newsletters, Shop Papers and Publications (Box 19, Folder 1)
- American Standard Inc., Annual Report, 1983 (Box 19, Item 1)
- Union Switch and Signal Location Study, September 20, 1985 (Box 19, Item 2)
- WABCO/Switch Project, PACE Business Retention Study, March 1986 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Midwest Center for Labor Research (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Correspondence with John Lichtenstein of American Standard, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- General Signal, Annual Report on Form 10-K, 1984 (Box 19, Item 3)
- Union Switch & Signal and WABCO Campaign - 1986 Through the Present (Box 19, Item 4)
- United Electrical Workers Correspondence, 1986 (Box 19, Item 5)
- Correspondence with Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company, 1983 (Box 19, Item 6)
- Track Houses Department 100 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- US Passenger Rail Technologies (Box 19, Item 7)
- A New Era: Annual Report of the Railway Progress Institute, 1984 (Box 19, Item 8)
- FCST SP&E, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- PACE (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Union Switch and Signal Receipts (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Midwest Center for Labor Research (Box 19, Folder 9)
- UE Local 610 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- US Steel Product Lines (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Coalition to Save the Break and Switch (Box 19, Folder 12)
- L&N Radnor Yard, 1980 (Box 19, Item 9)
- The Air Brake Equipment of China's Railway Today by Sha Mao-Shi, 1983 (Box 19, Item 10)
- WABCO, "26-LIC/CS-1" Electro-Pneumatic Brake Equipment, 1981 (Box 19, Item 11)
- New/Focus Issues (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Urban Mass Transit Authority Act (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Papers regarding Mass Transit (Box 20, Item 1)
- Plan and Forecast, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Union Switch and Signal Internal Correspondence, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Budget (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Salaries, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- JEMcC Staff Meetings (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Planning Transfer Team (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Foundry Reorganization (Box 20, Folder 9)
- United Electrical Workers and American Standard Miscellaneous Materials (Box 20, Folder 10)
- SAB Harmon Industries, Inc. Annual Report, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Correspondence regarding Contracts (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Wall Street (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Air Brakes (Box 20, Item 2)
- General Signal Annual Report, 1985 (Box 20, Item 3)
- IC Industries Annual Report, 1985 (Box 20, Item 4)
- WABCO Servotrol Brake Control Equipment for CIE/Dublin Suburban Railways (Box 20, Item 5)
- Papers regarding Union Switch and Signal (Box 20, Item 6)
- WABCO "MC-30A-1/CS-1" Electro-Pneumatic Brake Equipment for South African Transit Services Class 6M Suburban Trains (Box 20, Item 7)
- WABCO "26-C" Air Brake Control Equipment for MTA/Metro North Push Pull Cab & Trailer Cars (Box 20, Item 8)
- The Pocket List of Railroad Officials, 1985 (Box 20, Item 9)
- Budget, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Tri-State Policies, By-Laws and Personnel (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Industrial Renaissance Conference, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Calendar of Events, Monthly Log of Tri-State Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Carrie Furnace Information (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Conferences (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Computer Information (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 7-8)
- Duquesne Light Economic Development Fund, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Eastern Industrial Valleys Community of Faith, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- EDCS Tour and Equity Fund (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Eminent Domain Brochure, Early Tri-State Information (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Eminent Domain, Morse Cutting Tool (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Eminent Domain (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Eminent Domain, Municipal Authorities Act, Pennylvania (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Eminent Domain, NABISCO (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Federation for Industrial Retention and Renewal (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Employee Partnership Fund (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Labor History, Library, Video and Historical Markers (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Funding Information (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Plant Shutdowns Information, Grocery Stores (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Intern Information (Box 21, Folder 22)
- LTV Bankruptcy and Amsteel Information (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Media Information (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Mon Valley Tri-State Network (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Tri-State Information (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Needs Assessment Research (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Articles on Economy (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Press Releases, 1987-1989 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Tri-State Office Management, 1982-1986 (Box 22, Folder 7-9)
- Office Supplies and Equipment (Box 22, Folder 10)
- PACE Warehouse (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Local Labor Lists (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Politics (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Polka Benefit (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Rambling Man File (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Southbank Industry Association, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project Conference Information, December 7, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project Cleveland Base, Upper Ohio (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Resolutions (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Robotics Institute (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Starting Again and Pat Hanratty Conferences (Box 22, Folder 21)
- South Side Electrics (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Staff Time Sheets, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Tax IRS 501-C4 Status (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Town Forum CDBG/Pittsburgh (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Urban League (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Steel Valley Authority, General Information (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Steel Valley Authority By-Laws and Articles of Incorporation (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Steel Valley Authority Board Minutes, 1986-1988 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Literature Distributed by Tri-State, 1979-1984 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Local 1397 Food Bank, Clippings, 1982-1984 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Tri-State Conference Newsletters, 1981-1984, 1987-1989 (Box 23, Folder 10-11)
- Traveling Expense Sheets (Box 23, Folder 12)
- USWA Local 3403 Tri-State Unit Contracts (Box 23, Folder 13)
- South Side Steel (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Tri-State Membership Meeting (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Tri-State Political Action Committee (Box 23, Folder 16)
- USWA General and Legislative Information (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Video Equipment (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Voluntary Restraint Agreements (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Union and Non-Union Political Action Committees (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Denominational Ministry Strategy, Pledge Card Campaign/Mellon Bank (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Planned Manufacturing Districts (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Black Workers for Justice (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Homestead and Rankin (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Allegheny Conference on Community Development, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Allegheny County Development, 1978-1989 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- American Institute for Imported Steel, 1981-1983 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Allegheny Council on Civil Rights, South Africa Disinvestment, 1984-1987 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Ben Franklin Partnership, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Braddock's Field Historical Society Newsletter, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Capuchins Office of Justice and Peace, St. Augustine, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Carnegie Mellon University, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Catholic Bishops, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Center for Constitutional Rights (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Center for Democratic Renewal, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Christian Associates of Southwestern Pennsylvania, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Clean Water Action Project, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Cleveland Council of Unemployed Workers, 1985-1989 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Community of Celebration, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- CORA Newsletters, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Democratic Socialists of America (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Eastern Industrial Valleys Community of Faith (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Great Lakes Appalachian Project (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Greenham in London Newsletter, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Mill Hunk Herald (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Institute for Policy Studies, Washington DC, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Infrastructure (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Integrated Circuit (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Middle Tennessee State University Conference Paper, "Problems of Adaptation to Competition and Structural Change in Major Steel Markets" by Hans Mueller, 1983 (Box 24, Item 1)
- Lyndon LaRouche Information (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Interreligious Economic Crisis Organizing Network (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Indiana University of Pennsylvania Labor Studies (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Jewish Labor Committee (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Jobs with Peace, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Just Harvest (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Thomas Merton Center (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Micah Project, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Midwest Center for Labor Research (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Mon Valley Commission (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Mon Valley Expressway, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Mon Valley Initiative, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Mon Valley Progress Council, 1989-1991 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Mon Valley Renaissance, California University of Pennsylvania, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Mon Valley Unemployed Committee (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Mon-Yough Organization Information, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- NAACP (Box 25, Folder 17)
- National Anti-Klan Network (Box 25, Folder 18)
- National Business Incubator Association (Box 25, Folder 19)
- National Center for Policy Alternatives, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- National Committee for Full Employment, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- The National Council on Aging (Box 25, Folder 22)
- National Unemployed Network (Box 25, Folder 23)
- New Populist Forum (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Northeast-Midwest Institute (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Naugatuck Valley Project (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Peace Work Alternatives, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Pennsylvania Campaign for a Nuclear Weapons Freeze, 1985-1988 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Project for Economic Renewal of Communities, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Pennsylvania Council of the Arts, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Pennsylvania Rural Coalition (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Pennsylvania Public Interest Coalition (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Penn's Southwest Association, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- PACE of Philadelphia (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Philadelphia Unemployment Project, 1984-1991 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Pittsburgh City Council and Urban Redevelopment Authority, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Pittsburgh Foundation (Box 25, Folder 37)
- River City, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Seattle Worker Center (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Small Manufacturers Council, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Sparrows Point Unemployed Committee, Baltimore (Box 25, Folder 41)
- Interview with Ira Magaziner by Irwin Marcus, May 19, 1983 (Box 25, Item 1)
- Barry Bluestone Interview, May 19, 1983 (Box 25, Item 2)
- Ann Markusen Interview, April 28, 1983 (Box 25, Item 3)
- Sitting Around the Volcano: Poet and Novelist Meridel LeSueur Speaks about Culture and Economic Change, 1984 (Box 25, Item 4)
- Select Proceedings of the IUP Conference on Industry and Society, The Industrial North: the Future of Jobs, Productivity and Community, October 21-23, 1982 (Box 25, Item 5)
- Rainbow Kitchen, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Southwestern Pennsylvania Industrial Resource Center (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Steel Valley C.O.G. (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Steel Valley United for Economic Progress (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Teamsters for a Democratic Union (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Tennessee Industrial Renewal Network, 1987-1989 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Three Rivers Labor Management Association (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Tri-State Economic Justice Network, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- University of Pittsburgh, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Westinghouse Foundation (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Women of Steel (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Workers Education Center, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Contacts (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Religious, Political and Union Contacts (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Ku Klux Klan (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Pennsylvania Studies and Reports (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Employee Stock Ownership Plans Information (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Residents Committee, Homstead and Munhall (Box 26, Folder 19-24)
- Residents Committee, Clairton Contacts (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Residents Committees, Participatory Research (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Residents Committees, Dislocated Workers Survey (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Residents Committees, Duquesne Contacts (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Residents Committee, East Pittsburgh (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Residents Committee, McKeesport Contacts (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Residents Committee, Turtle Creek (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Steel Valley Unemployed Center, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Allegheny County Elected Officials, 1989-1994 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- Plant Shutdowns (Box 26, Folder 34)
- PACE of Pittsburgh Consulting Group (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program Retreat, Wheeling, WV (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Employee Stock Ownership Plan Conference, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program Conference, December 7, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 2-8)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project Literature (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project, Ohio Contacts (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Making Industrial America Competitive Again, Address by Jerry V. Jarrett of AmeriTrust Corporation, March 13, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Ohio Plant Closings, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project Ohio, LTV Cleveland Works Impact Study, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project Ohio, Owens-Corning Fiberglass (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project Ohio, Rainbow Coalition (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Reports regarding the Regional Reindustrialization Program, 1986, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 16)